(Sheldon:)...which are only effective against
wraiths and daywalkers...
...and there are no more left.
The cards remaining in the stack are:
(Sheldon:)Four fire weapons, a troll,
two ogres and the Jewel of Osiris.
(Leonard:)See? Ruined.
(Penny:)Sheldon, that is incredible.
(Sheldon:)From your vantage point,
it certainly must seem so.
(Leonard:)Sheldon has kind of
a photographic memory.
"Photographic" is a misnomer.
(Sheldon:)I have an eidetic memory,
as I've told you many times.
(Sheldon:)Most recently last year during lunch
on the afternoon of May 7th.
(Sheldon:)You had turkey
and complained it was dry.
(Howard:)Well, I guess game's over.
(Penny:)Really? Oh, great.
I mean, aww....
(Penny:)-Okay, I gotta go.
-Why?
Because last time I didn't go,
I ended up playing Mystic Warlords of Ka.
Not "Ka." Ka-ah.
-Bye.
-See you.